Hello hello everyone how are you all I am
your personal advisor Amit Raj Sharma and
you are watching Yudh Real you know
that Max Bupa Health Insurance Company has now
become Nav Up Health Insurance Company
so let's know the
details of Rupa Realities and health insurance policy
first of all the entry limit is from
18 years to 65 years you get the plan
in both the categories
individual as well as family floater
point system in this you get to
see one year two year three years that
means if you want to take health insurance for 2 years or 3
years together you
can do that in this you also get cover for Kabir
in this the
first 15 days of the policy is the only waiting
period for this there is a back cover in it of
sum insured which is limited and from 3 lakh
rupees to 1 crore rupees you
get the option of spoon sonth in this you get
world cover for second medical opinion
when we need it when we are hospitalized
in this major condition  So, if you
need a second expert,
that is also covered. There is no typo on these network room rents. There are
different
categories of people to understand. So, you know that somewhere
you will get a standard AC room, somewhere
you will get a deluxe room, somewhere you
may get a standard AC room. So,
it will depend on understanding, but there is no
typo on every room rent. Alternative
treatment is fine. There is a difference between treatment to misled
treatment, organ donor transportation,
that is, treatment of OM where
you may need dialysis or chemotherapy, a
tractor. Meaning,
such problems are not likely to arise with districts.
You get all these benefits of
conductor and modern treatment in this plan.
You
know that nowadays new technologies keep coming.
Robotic surgery is also quite popular, so there is
cardiac surgery, there is cell therapy,
immunotherapy and other advanced
treatments, you get covered inside.
Now to the immortal shot, but yes,
some robotic surgeries, such as this, you have to
see the sub-limit of only up to one lakh rupees.  You
get a road ambulance, you get
hospitalization for ₹500.
In air ambulance, that is, the ambulance which is an airplane,
if there is reimbursement then there is a limit of 2.5 lakh rupees.
If it is cashless then up to the understanding
controller is there. Your provider should be
from India. Right, share accommodation. You all
know that when we are admitted in the hospital
and if we share our room with someone, then
we
get cash benefit on share condition. From 800 rupees
per day to 4800 rupees per year limit. From 1000 rupees
per day to 6000
rupees per year limit. Why is it in two categories
because it depends on how much you are taking.
Right, if the news is ₹10 then you will
easily get ₹1000. Below that, then
you will get less right
benefits. And if you are hospitalized for 48 hours,
then this benefit will be available here. Then
you have a waiting period of only 15 days
for checkup. If needed, read  The condition is such that if you have taken the
policy individually
then you will get maximum up to ₹5000, if you
take family floater from every moment then
you can get maximum up to Rs.10000.
Booster benefit means
what we call your no claim bonus here,
it is called booster benefit which is
hundred percent as per your understanding, if the first year is
clear free then 50%, if the second year is also
clear free then also you will get 50%, in this
way you will get 100%
booster benefit as per your understanding, free hospitalization in this
you are getting seven days, post
hospitalization you are getting 180 days,
now comes the matter of automatic restoration
which we call automatic recharge,
some people also call it recharge benefit,
it is unlimited means up to the understanding
how many times you will keep getting it within a year,
now when it comes to optional news,
first is personal accidental time, you will get
live time in this as per your understanding, the
maximum will be up to one crore, it should be  At
least 18 years right, in this,
mental disability or parcel disability on accidental death
is also covered,
hence you can take hospital gas benefit
in Kabir and office, if we understand it to be of Rs 5 lakh then
₹1000 per day, support from 7.5 lakh to
15 lakh and then it will be ₹2000
per day, but if you have taken a spoonful of fennel, that is, if you have taken
sum insured of
Rs 15 lakh, then you will get ₹4000 per day
in it, the option of cash benefit safeguard is
also available in it, first you get it by
saving the claim, what does it mean
that there is a list of non-parcel items,
which we do not get on health insurance morale items, then you will find
their claim inside, there will be a
bad list inside it,
you will have to read it, if it is written on the items then
you will get the news about it, that too half a
spoon and still the option of
booster benefits of guard is available in it, what does it mean,
now Muslims cannot earn more than Rs 50 thousand  If it goes
within a year, then there is
not going to be any effect on the booster benefit,
meaning there will be no difference. In this plan
also, you have live health benefits, that is,
you can call it the health program,
if you remain healthy, keep walking 1000 steps at
night continuously, keeping yourself completely
fit, the application of this I will
tell you, which
you will have to download within 30 days of taking the policy,
now if you renew the policy in it,
you will get a discount. The waiting period
which is of 15 days initially is per
day for normal hospitalization, there is
no waiting period in accidental case, there is a waiting period of 24 months
on pre-specified conditions and
you will probably not get to see the cover in this, you are getting a
pre-existing waiting period of 36 months, that is, the
digit which has been going on earlier,
Anand Gupta ji had commented, sir,
thank you, I want to tell you that the
video of Gautam Aristo is already available on the channel
and what you wrote today and Yash
and  We have shared its video with you today, so
you have both the videos,
thank you, you can download it here and
you will have to see the premium yourself because the location, which is
Noida, will depend on many things,
you will get the rest of the PDF on the Telegram channel also,
thank you so much, please like this
video if you want us to keep
working according to your questions, thank
you.